Nogizaka46 12th Birthday
The annual birthday live to celebrate the debut of the group
This time, it was held at Saitama Super Arena for 4 days!
Just before the birthday live was a great success
there was a girl who tried her hand at running errands!
There was a girl who challenged to run an errand!
Aya Ogawa!
She is 16 years and 8 months old and still in the prime of wanting to be pampered.
Loved by all the members
She is the youngest member of Nagisa 46!
Just before the second day of the live
Captain Umezawa, seeing the timing
and calls Aya to him.
The errand is about to begin!
Here, sit here.
Sit here.
Aya, do you know what day it is today?
It's the birthday concert, right? Yes!
It's Nogizaka's birthday. We need a big cake for everyone.
There's a cake shop nearby.
I was going to buy it, but I have a meeting.
That's why I wanted to ask Aya.
Alone? Yeah, alone. It's so lonely.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Yes, Aya is the only one I can ask. I see.
Can you do it? I'll try my best.
Can you hang in there? Yeah, thanks. The big one.
Yes, a big one
Umezawa is convinced that Aya can do it.
And I'll add this request.
Um, do you see the flags of the members outside the venue?
Yes, ma'am.
There are flags and panels of the members outside the venue.
They send flags to the fans, too.
It's also a photo spot for fans.
If Aya takes a picture in front of my flag there
I thought I could do my best at the show.
It's before the show, so there are a lot of fans there.
If they find out, they'll surround Aya.
I'm scared. But is that okay?
Of course, I'm a little nervous.
But I'll do my best for you.
Really? Can you do it? Can we take a picture?
I'm so excited! Then take two shots with me.
Here's your money.
I want to put in more money.
Aya is very enthusiastic about the cake.
From the live venue, Saitama Super Arena, to the cake shop
It's almost a straight road for 500 meters.
After picking up the cake, we headed back to the venue
I'm going to try to take a picture with Umezawa-san's flag!
I'm off!
Have a good day!
If anything dangerous happens, I'll be right there.
Good luck!
See you later.
Hide it.
Bye bye.
Be careful.
Don't let the customers see you.
Your disguise is perfect.
But she looks a little nervous.
Aya's errand runner is about to begin.
I'm so nervous!
We're outside the venue.
This is what it looks like outside.
It's my first time.
Can you do it?
I'm hungry.
I've only eaten strawberries today.
I've been rehearsing since this morning, and all I've eaten is strawberries, so I'm going to be a hungry adult already.
Hungry adult, Aya!
So far, it looks like we're off to a good start!
Wow, wow, there are so many fans!
I can't see much of them.
I want to, but I can't!
Oh, it's so strange!
Oh, my gosh!
Is that a flag? Is that a flag? Flag?
I've never seen it from the outside like this.
Wow!
I didn't know it looked like this.
Heh heh heh.
I feel like I'm getting a little more relaxed now.
Ha~!
High end walkway
Right, left, right!
Aya learned from Mr. Umezawa to cross the crosswalk with her hands up. She's doing great.
She made it!
It's a slope!
Climbing up the hill.
First time running an errand...
I'm so happy!
I wonder if any of you are walking now.
How many more hours?
In a few hours.
I'm sure there are some of you
I'm sure there will be some of you
I'm looking forward to it.
This one's pretty, but it's no F-loser.
Hello.
Forty-four.
I'm suddenly embarrassed.
Aya, I'm so tired.
Are we there yet?
Still not ready?
And here...
I saw two guys sneaking up behind me.
Excuse me.
I'm Aya Ozawa.
This is Aya.
Excuse me.
A fan noticed them and called out to them.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
I couldn't help it.
Thank you for coming to run errands at the cake shop.
I'll see you at the concert in a few hours.
Thank you.
I'm so happy for you.
With some nice encounters
We've managed to arrive at the cake shop in one piece!
I'm sorry to disturb you.
Hello.
I reserved a cake at Umezawa.
Yes, please.
Yes, I'll be waiting.
Thank you very much.
I'm so relieved that I said it so well.
And here it is...
Oh, my God!
What a surprise!
I found my favorite tomatoes at the cake shop!
Thank you so much!
That's so cute!
A big cake that all the members can eat!
The plate was also custom made for this occasion!
We'll put it in a box for you.
Thank you very much!
Bon appétit!
I'm so excited about this gorgeous cake!
But what I'm really interested in is...
Tomatoes!
I want to eat tomatoes!
Can I buy tomatoes?
I think I'll buy tomatoes.
You said I could buy anything.
Can I buy some tomatoes?
Can I have this one too?
Yes, thank you.
Mr. Umezawa said yes.
I got the cake, too.
It's okay. It's okay.
It's so cute!
It's so big!
I wonder if I can take it home.
Here you go, sir.
Thank you very much.
A very big cake!
The kind waitress handed it to me at the entrance of the store.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
Aya, your first errand is clear!
Okay, I left, but I'm already heavy.
Okay, now that I've left Kenke.
Next, I'm going to take pictures with Umezawa-san's plugs
I'm going to be later than I left.
Hehehe.
I was just getting it together.
I can't raise my hand.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't put my hand up.
Here we go.
I feel like I've lost so much weight, but it's okay.
The precious cake we all eat together
I hope it didn't fall apart
I've got the flag on my heart
I'm so nervous!
I wonder if I'll be okay
The biggest challenge is at the end of this escalator.
It's right in front of the venue, which is packed with guests.
Sounds like fun, but
I'm nervous, nervous, nervous!
Help me, help me!
Somebody help me!
Help me!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, help!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, no!
Help me!
Oh, my God, the seller.
Oh, my God.
This place...
You're allowed to sell this place?
Oh, my God.
I'm so excited.
It's fun, but I feel...
It's like, "Oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They look like they're having so much fun.
Here you go, you're so cute.
I'm so embarrassed!
Help!
There it is.
I'm so nervous!
Help me!
What should I do?
The guy who's filming...
I wonder if I should get in line.
Here.
I've never done this before.
I don't know how to do it.
It's so new to me.
I don't know, Aya.
I'm so embarrassed.
Help!
You're filming here?
You're filming here all by yourself?
Such a big KENKEMON!
What should I do with this?
No, I took this selfie.
I have no choice but to take it.
I don't know...
I'll take a picture with it.
What should I do?
I don't think I'm brave enough to ask someone to take it.
I'll just take the picture by myself.
Shay-show!
Oh no, oh no, oh no, I'll make you wait!
Help me, help me, help me!
I'm struggling with the direction of the flag!
Oh, here it comes!
This is so hard, so hard!
Shayesho
It's a little difficult.
How's that? Is that good? Is that good?
A perfect shot!
He showed off his advanced technique of including his own flag in the shot.
In fact, there were many fans around who noticed and warmly watched me.
Wow, I see... it would have been best if I had someone take a picture of me.
I didn't have the courage to do that.
I'm sorry!
But I'm sure I could have.
With this, all of today's errands were completed!
The show is about to start, so I'm rushing to Umezawa-san's place.
Oh, I see it! I can see the goal!
Oh, I'm so tired!
Mr. Umezawa has been fidgeting like this during the errand.
Captain worried about the youngest member.
She already has a mother's expression on her face.
Almost to the room where Umezawa's mom is waiting!
Aya-chan is on her last spurt of errands!
Almost to the room where Umezawa-mama is waiting!
Welcome home!
I'm home!
Welcome home
I bought this. With such a big thing. It's so heavy.
I saw tomatoes on sale, so I bought some.
How cute. You bought tomatoes?
I gave him more money and he bought tomatoes?
Buy me a better one. It's good.
These tomatoes look good, too.
It looks really delicious.
Thanks. It was heavy.
Are you okay? They didn't notice?
I think they did.
Welcome back. Thank you. They'll be happy to see you.
I'm glad you could make it, Aya. Thank you.
I'm going to open the cake I worked so hard to bring.
I'll get the ribbon.
It's so big.
I think we'll have enough for everyone.
Let's open it together. Ready?
Wow!
It's a little, it's a little bit on my shoulder!
Is it my imagination?
It's a little crooked this way.
It fell apart a little bit, but the decoration part is fine.
No problem at all!
Everyone will be happy with this.
I'm sure everyone will be happy with it.
When I told them that Arya bought it, they were so happy.
They are so proud of it.
Let's all eat this later.
I can do my best for someone.
I can do my best because everyone is here.
I'm sure Aya's hard work will reach everyone.
After the concert
In front of the backstage, there were senpai (senpai) and Aya-chan, who were chewing on the cake with a delicious smile.
Aya-chan was a little bit proud of herself.
Nogizaka46 has entered its 13th year
Nogizaka46 will continue to grow with the rekindling of its strong spirit!
Thank you for watching!